<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
- Copyright 2020 Han Young <hanyoung@protonmail.com>
- Copyright 2020 Devin Lin <espidev@gmail.com>
- SPDX-License-Identifier: GPL-2.0-or-later
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kclock</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <name>Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">الساعة</name>
  <name xml:lang="ast">Reló</name>
  <name xml:lang="bg">Часовник</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Rellotge</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Rellotge</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Hodiny</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Ur</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Uhr</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Ρολόι</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Horloĝo</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Reloj</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Kell</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Erlojua</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kello</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Horloge</name>
  <name xml:lang="ga">Clog</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Reloxo</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">שעון</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">घड़ी</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Óra</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Clock (Horologio)</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Orologio</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">საათი</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">시계</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Laikrodis</name>
  <name xml:lang="lv">Pulkstenis</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Klok</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Klokke</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਘੜੀ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Zegar</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Relógio</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Relógio</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Ceas</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Часы</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">घटिका</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Hodiny</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Clock</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Klocka</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Saat</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Годинник</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">时钟</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">時鐘</name>
  <summary>Keep time and set alarms</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">حافظ على الوقت واضبط المنبهات</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="bg">Показване на часа и задаване на аларми</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Aneu a l'hora i establiu alarmes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aneu fins a l'hora i establiu alarmes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Ponechat čas a nastavit upomínky</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Hold styr på tiden og indstil alarmer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Im Takt bleiben und Alarme festlegen</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Keep time and set alarms</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Teni daton kaj meti alarmoj</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Marque la hora y defina alarmas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Mantendu ordua eta alarmak ezarri</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Näytä kellonaika ja aseta hälytyksiä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Conserver l'heure et définir des alarmes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Vexa a hora e poña alarmas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">התנהלות עם הזמן והגדרת התראות</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Időmérés és riasztások beállítása</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Mantene tempore e assigna alarmas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Jaga waktu dan setel alarm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Tieni il tempo e imposta gli allarmi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">ადევნეთ თვალყური დროს და დააყენეთ განგაშები</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">시간을 보고 알람을 설정</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lt">Sekti laiką ir nusistatyti žadintuvus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="lv">Sekojiet laikam un lieciet modinātājus</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Tijd bijhouden en wekkers zetten</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Vis klokka og still inn alarmar</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Pilnuj czasu i ustawiaj alarmy</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Manter o horário e configurar os alarmes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Duce evidența timpului și stabilește alarme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Просмотр времени и установка напоминаний</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">समयं रक्षन्तु, अलार्मं च सेट् कुर्वन्तु</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Upošteva čas in nastavlja alarme</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Håll tiden och ställ in alarm</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Zaman Tutucusu ve Alarm Kurucusu</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Розклад та встановлення нагадувань</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">显示时间和设置闹钟</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">看時間並設定鬧鐘</summary>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <description>
    <p>A universal clock application for desktop and mobile. Clock includes a stopwatch and a world clock, and allows you to set multiple alarms and timers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">تطبيق ساعة عالمي لسطح المكتب والهاتف المحمول. يتضمن التطبيق ساعة توقيت وساعة عالمية، ويسمح لك بتعيين منبهات ومؤقتات متعددة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Универсално приложение за часовник за десктоп и мобилно устройство. Часовникът включва хронометър и световен часовник и ви позволява да зададете множество аларми и таймери.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Una aplicació universal de rellotge per a l'escriptori i mòbil. El rellotge inclou un cronòmetre i un rellotge mundial, i permet establir alarmes i temporitzadors diversos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Una aplicació universal de rellotge per a l'escriptori i mòbil. El rellotge inclou un cronòmetre i un rellotge mundial, i permet establir alarmes i temporitzadors diversos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Univerzální aplikace hodin pro stolní počítače a mobilní zařízení. Hodiny obsahují stopky a světové hodiny a umožňují nastavit více budíků a časovačů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Eine universelle Uhren-Anwendung für Plasma. Clock enthält eine Stoppuhr und eine Weltzeituhr. Zudem können mehrere Alarme und Zeitlimits festgelegt werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">A universal clock application for desktop and mobile. Clock includes a stopwatch and a world clock, and allows you to set multiple alarms and timers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Universala horloĝa aplikaĵo por labortablo kaj poŝtelefono. Horloĝo inkluzivas tempumilon kaj mondan horloĝon, kaj permesas vin agordi plurajn alarmojn kaj tempumilojn.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Una aplicación de reloj universal para el escritorio y el móvil. El reloj incluye un cronómetro y un reloj mundial, además de permitirle definir múltiples alarmas y temporizadores.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Mahaigainerako eta mugikorrerako erloju-aplikazio unibertsal bat. Erlojuak kronometroa eta munduko-erlojua ditu, eta hainbat alarma eta tenporizadore ezartzeko aukera eskaintzen dizu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Yleinen kellosovellus työpöydälle ja mobiiliin. Sisältää sekunti- ja maailmankellot sekä mahdollisuus asettaa useampia hälytyksiä ja ajastimia.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Une application d'horloge universelle pour ordinateur de bureau et mobile. L'horloge comprend un chronomètre et une horloge mondiale. Elle vous permet aussi de définir plusieurs alarmes et minuteries.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Unha aplicación universal de reloxo para escritorio e para móbil. Inclúe un cronómetro e un reloxo universal, e permite poñer varias alarmas e temporizadores.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">יישום שעון אוניברסלי למחשב ולניידים. השעון כולל שעון עצר ושעון עולמי ומאפשר להגדיר מגוון התראות וקוצבי זמן.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Univerzális óraalkalmazás asztali és mobil eszközökre. Az óra tartalmaz egy stopperórát és világórát, valamint lehetővé teszi több riasztás és időzítők beállítását.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Un application de horologio universal per scriptorio e mobile. Horologio include un  chronometro e un horologio mundial, e tu pote sempre fixar alarmas e timers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Aplikasi jam universal untuk desktop dan ponsel. Jam ini dilengkapi dengan stopwatch dan jam dunia, serta memungkinkan Anda menyetel beberapa alarm dan pengatur waktu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Un'applicazione universale per l'orologio per desktop e per mobile. Orologio include un cronometro e un orologio mondiale, e ti permette di impostare più allarmi e timer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">უნივერსალური საათის აპლიკაცია კომპიუტერისა და მობილურისთვის. Clock შეიცავს წამზომს და მსოფლიო საათს და საშუალებას გაძლევთ, ერთზე მეტი განგაში და წამზომი დააყენოთ.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">데스크톱과 모바일용 다기능 시계 앱입니다. 초시계, 세계 시간, 다중 알람과 타이머 설정 기능이 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Universali laikrodžio programa, skirta kompiuteriams ir mobiliesiems įrenginiams. Laikrodis leidžia nustatyti daug žadintuvų bei laikmačių, be to, jame yra chronometras ir pasaulio laikrodžiai.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Universāla pulksteņa lietotne datoram un viedierīcēm. Pulkstenis satur hronometru un pasaules pulksteni, kā arī ļauj uzlikt dažādus modinātājus un taimerus.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Een universele kloktoepassing voor bureaublad en mobiel. Kclock omvat een stopwatch en een wereldklok en biedt u het zetten meerdere wekkers en timers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Eit universelt klokkeprogram for skrivebord og mobil. Inneheld stoppeklokke og verdsklokke, og lèt deg stilla inn fleire alarmar og nedteljarar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Wszechstronny zegar na urządzenia przenośne i biurkowe. Zegar zawiera stoper oraz zegar światowy. Umożliwia ustawienie wielu alarmów i minutników.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Um aplicativo de relógio universal para desktop e celular. O relógio inclui um cronômetro e um relógio mundial, e permite que você defina vários alarmes e timers.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Aplicație de ceas universal pentru birou și mobil. Ceasul include un cronometru și ora pe glob, și vă permite să stabiliți multiple alarme și temporizatori.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Универсальные часы для стационарных компьютеров и мобильных устройств. В программе есть секундомер и мировые часы, поддерживается установка напоминаний и таймеров.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">डेस्कटॉप् तथा मोबाईल् इत्येतयोः कृते एकः सार्वभौमिकः घण्टा-अनुप्रयोगः । घण्टायां स्टॉपवॉच्, विश्वघटिका च सन्ति, तथा च बहुविधाः अलार्म-समयनिर्धारकाः सेट् कर्तुं शक्नुवन्ति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Univerzalna aplikacija ure za namizne in mobilne naprave. Ura vključuje štoparico in svetovno uro ter omogoča nastavitev več alarmov in časovnikov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ett universellt klockprogram för stationära datorer och mobiler. Klockan innehåller ett stoppur och en världsklocka och låter dig ställa in flera alarm och tidtagare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Masaüstü ve taşınabilir aygıtlar için evrensel bir saat uygulaması. Saat, bir kronometre ve dünya saati içerir ve birden çok alarm ve sayaç kurmanıza olanak tanır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Універсальна програма-будильник для робочих станцій та мобільних пристроїв. Реалізовано таймер та загальносвітовий годинник, можна встановлювати декілька нагадувань та таймерів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">一款同时支持桌面和手机环境的时钟应用。带有秒表和世界时钟，还可以设置多个闹钟和计时器。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">桌面與手機通用的時鐘應用程式。《時鐘》包含碼錶與世界時鐘功能，也讓您設定多個鬧鐘和計時器。</p>
    <p>It contains alarm, timer, stopwatch and timezone functionalities. Alarms and timers are able to wake the device from suspend on Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يحتوي على وظائف التنبيه والمؤقت وساعة التوقيت والمنطقة الزمنية. المنبهات والمؤقتات قادرة على إيقاظ الجهاز من حالة التعليق على البلازما.</p>
    <p xml:lang="bg">Той съдържа функции за аларма, таймер, хронометър и часова зона. Алармите и таймерите могат да събудят устройството на Plasma от състояние на приспиване.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Conté funcions d'alarma, temporitzador, cronòmetre i zona horària. Les alarmes i els temporitzadors també poden fer que el dispositiu deixi d'estar suspès en el Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Conté funcions d'alarma, temporitzador, cronòmetre i zona horària. Les alarmes i els temporitzadors també poden fer que el dispositiu deixe d'estar suspés en Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Obsahuje funkce budíku, časovače, stopek a časového pásma. Budíky a časovače jsou schopny probudit zařízení z režimu spánku v prostředí Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Sie beinhaltet einen Wecker, einen Timer, eine Stoppuhr und Zeitzonenfunktionen. Der Wecker und der Timer können Ihr Gerät aus dem Standby-Modus aufzuwecken, sofern Sie Plasma verwenden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">It contains alarm, timer, stopwatch and timezone functionalities. Alarms and timers are able to wake the device from suspend on Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Ĝi enhavas alarmon, tempigilon, kronometron kaj horzonajn funkciojn. Alarmoj kaj tempigiloj kapablas veki la aparaton de suspendo sur Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Contiene las funciones de alarma, temporizador, cronómetro y zona horaria. Las alarmas y los temporizadores pueden despertar el dispositivo del estado de suspensión en Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Alarma, tenporizadorea, kronometroa eta ordu-eremu funtzionalitateak ditu. Alarmak eta tenporizadoreak gailua esekiduratik esnatzeko gai dira.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Sisältää hälytys-, ajastin, sekuntikello- ja aikavyöhyketoiminnot. Hälytykset ja ajastimet voivat Plasmassa herättää laitteen keskeytystilasta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Elle contient des fonctionnalités d'alarmes, de chronomètres, de minuteurs et de fuseaux horaires. Les alarmes et minuteurs sont aussi capables de faire sortir le périphérique du mode de veille lors de l'utilisation de Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Ten funcionalidades de alarma, temporizador, cronómetro, e fuso horario. As alarmas e os temporizadores poden espertar o dispositivo da suspensión en Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">הוא מכיל יכולות כגון התראות, קוצב זמן, שעון עצר ושעון עולמי. התראות וקוצבי זמן יכולים להעיר את המכשיר מהשהייה בפלזמה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">प्लाज़्मा के लिए एक संसृत घड़ी अनुप्रयोग। इसमें अलार्म, टाइमर,  विराम घड़ी और समय क्षेत्र विषेशताएँ शामिल हैं। प्लाज़्मा का उपयोग करते समय अलार्म उपकरण को तंत्र निलंबन से जगाने में भी सक्षम होते हैं।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Tartalmaz riasztás, időzítő, stopper és időzóna funkciókat. Plasma használatakor az ébresztők és az időzítők képesek felébreszteni az eszközt felfüggesztett állapotból.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Il contine functionalitate de alarmas,chronometro, campana de horologio (stopwatch) e fusos horari. Alarmas e chronometros es capace de eveliar le dispositivo ab suspensiones in Plasma. </p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Berisi fungsionalitas alarm, timer, stopwatch, dan zona waktu. Alarm dan timer juga dapat membangunkan peranti dari tidur di Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Contiene le funzionalità di allarme, timer, cronometro e fuso orario. Gli allarmi e i timer possono risvegliare il dispositivo dalla sospensione se si utilizza Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">ის განგაშის, ტაიმერის, წამზომის და დროის სარტყლის ფუნქციებს მოიცავს. მაღვიძარას და ტაიმერებს შეუძლიათ გააღვიძონ მოწყობილობა, თუ Plasma გაშვებულია.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">알람, 타이머, 초시계, 시간대 기능을 지원합니다. Plasma를 사용 중일 때 장치를 절전 모드에서 알람이나 타이머로 깨울 수도 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lt">Ją sudaro žadintuvo, laikmačio, chronometro ir laiko juostų funkcionalumai. Plasma aplinkoje žadintuvai ir laikmačiai turi galimybę pažadinti sistemą iš pristabdymo būsenos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="lv">Programmai ir signāla, taimera, hronometra un laika zonu funkcijas. Signāli un taimeri ļauj ierīci ar„Plasma“ pamodināt pēc iesnaudināšanas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het bevat de functionaliteiten wekker, timer, stopwatch en tijdzone. Wekkers kunnen het apparaat uit status onderbroken laten ontwaken bij gebruik van Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Det inneheld alarmklokke, nedteljing, stoppeklokke og støtte for ulike tidssonar. Alarmar og nedteljing kan vekkja maskina frå kvilemodus på Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pa">ਇਸ ਵਿੱਚ ਅਲਾਰਮ, ਟਾਈਮਰ, ਸਟਾਪ-ਵਾਚ ਅਤੇ ਸਮਾਂ-ਖੇਤਰ ਦੀਆਂ ਸਹੂਲਤਾਂ ਹਨ। ਪਲਾਜ਼ਮਾ ਉੱਤੇ ਅਲਾਰਮ ਤੇ ਟਾਈਮਰ ਸਸਪੈਂਡ ਤੋਂ ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਨੂੰ ਚਾਲੂ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹਨ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Zawiera alarm, czasomierz, stoper oraz różne strefy czasowe. Alarmy i czasomierze są także w stanie wybudzić urządzenie z uśpienia na Plazmie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Contém funcionalidades de alarmes, temporizadores, cronómetros e fusos-horários. Os alarmes também conseguirão acordar o dispositivo da suspensão ao usar o Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Ele contém alarme, temporizador, cronômetro e funcionalidades de fuso horário. Os alarmes e temporizadores são capazes de acordar o dispositivo da suspensão no Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Are funcții de alarmă, cronometru, temporizator și fus orar. Alarmele și cronometrele pot trezi dispozitivul din somn, în Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности работы с напоминаниями, таймерами, секундомером и часовыми поясами. Напоминания и таймеры позволяют возобновить работу устройства после приостановки в Plasma.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">अस्मिन् अलार्म, टाइमर्, स्टॉपवॉच्, टाइम्जोन् कार्यक्षमता च सन्ति । अलार्मः, टाइमर् च प्लाज्मायां निलम्बनात् यन्त्रं जागृतुं समर्थाः सन्ति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Vsebuje alarm, odštevalnik časa, štoparico in funkcionalnost časovnih pasov. Alarm je sposoben tudi aktivirati napravo iz mirovanja, kadar uporablja Plasmo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Det innehåller alarm, tidtagning, stoppur och tidszonsfunktioner. Alarm och tidtagare kan också väcka enheten från viloläge när Plasma används.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Alarm, sayaç, kronometre ve zaman dilimi işlevlerini içerir. Alarmlar ve sayaçlar, aygıtı Plasma’da iken uykudan uyandırabilir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Передбачено будильник, таймер та секундомір, а також функціональні можливості з роботи у різних часових поясах. Будильники і таймери здатні пробуджувати пристрій зі стану сну, якщо на ньому використовується Плазма.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">它包含闹钟、计时器、秒表和时区功能。闹钟和计时器能够在 Plasma 上唤醒设备。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">它包含鬧鐘、計時器、碼錶與時區的功能。鬧鐘和計時器在使用 Plasma 時可以將裝置從睡眠中喚醒。</p>
  </description>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kclock.desktop</launchable>
  <recommends>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kclock.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Mobile view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض المحمول</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Изглед за мобилно устройство</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista al mòbil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista en el mòbil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Mobilní pohled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Mobile Ansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Προβολή για κινητά</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Mobile view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Poŝtelefona vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista móvil</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Mugikor ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Mobiilinäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage pour mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista de móbil.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגה לניידים</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">मोबाइल दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Mobilnézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de Mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan ponsel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista mobile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მობილური ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">모바일 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Mobilusis rodinys</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Viedtālruņa skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Beeld op mobiel</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Mobilvising</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਮੋਬਾਈਲ ਝਲਕ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok na urz. przenośne</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Versão para dispositivos móveis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Vista do celular</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Vizualizare mobilă</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Вид на мобильном устройстве</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">मोबाईल दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Mobilni pogled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Mobil vy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Taşınabilir görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Вигляд на мобільному пристрої</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">移动设备视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">行動版檢視</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kclock/kclock-mobile-timezones.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Desktop view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض سطح المكتب</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Изглед за десктоп системи</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista a l'escriptori</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de l'escriptori</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled pracovní plochy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Arbeitsflächenansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Προβολή για υπολογιστή γραφείου</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Desktop view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Labortabla vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de escritorio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Mahaigaineko ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Työpöytänäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage de bureau</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista de escritorio.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת מחשב</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">डेस्कटॉप दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Asztali nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de Scriptorio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan desktop</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista desktop</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">სამუსაო მაგიდის ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">데스크톱 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Darbalaukio rodinys</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Datora skats</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Beeld op bureaublad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Skrivebordsvising</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਡੈਸਕਟਾਪ ਝਲਕ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok na urz. biurkowe</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Versão para computador</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Vista da área de trabalho</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Vizualizare pentru birou</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Вид на настольном ПК</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">डेस्कटॉप दृश्यम्</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Namizni pogled</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Skrivbordsvy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Masaüstü görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Вигляд на комп'ютері</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">桌面视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">桌面版檢視</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kclock/kclock-desktop-timezones.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Timers page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">صفحة المؤقتات</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Страница с таймери</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Pàgina dels temporitzadors</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pàgina dels temporitzadors</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Stránka s časovači</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Timersiden</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Timer-Seite</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Σελίδα χρονοδιακοπτών</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Timers page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Temporiziloj paĝo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página de temporizadores</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Tenporizadoreen orria</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Ajastinsivu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Page de chronomètres</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Páxina dos temporizadores.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד קוצבי זמן</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">टाइमरों का पृष्ठ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Időzítők oldal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Pagina de chronometros</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Halaman timer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Pagina dei timer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">წამმზომების გვერდი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">타이머 쪽</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Laikmačių puslapis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Taimeru lapa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Pagina met timers</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Nedteljarside</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਟਾਈਮਰ ਸਫ਼ਾ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Strona czasomierzy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Página de Temporizadores</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Página dos temporizadores</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Pagina temporizatorilor</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Страница таймеров</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">टाइमर्स पृष्ठ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Stran merilnikov časa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Sida med tidtagningar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Sayaçlar sayfası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Сторінка таймерів</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">计时器页面</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">計時器列表頁面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kclock/kclock-mobile-timers.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Timer page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">صفحة المؤقت</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Страница на таймера</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Pàgina del temporitzador</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pàgina del temporitzador</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Stránka s časovačem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Timersiden</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Timer-Seite</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Σελίδα χρονοδιακόπτη</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Timer page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Timer-paĝo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página del temporizador</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Tenporizadorearen orria</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Ajastinsivu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Page de chronomètre</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Páxina dun temporizador.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד קוצב זמן</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">टाइमर पृष्ठ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Időzítő oldal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Pagiona de chronometro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Halaman timer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Pagina del timer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">წამმზომის გვერდი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">타이머 쪽</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Laikmačio puslapis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Taimera lapa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Pagina met timer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Nedteljingsside</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਟਾਈਮਰ ਸਫ਼ਾ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Strona czasomierza</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Página do Temporizador</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Página do temporizador</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Pagina temporizatorului</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Страница таймера</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">टाइमर पृष्ठ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Stran merilnika časa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Sida med tidtagning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Sayaç sayfası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Сторінка таймера</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">计时器页面</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">計時器頁面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kclock/kclock-desktop-timer.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Stopwatch page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">ساعة الإيقاف</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Страница на хронометъра</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Pàgina del cronòmetre</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pàgina del cronòmetre</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Stránka se stopkami</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Stopursiden</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Stoppuhrseite</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Σελίδα χρονομέτρου</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Stopwatch page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Kronometropaĝo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página del cronómetro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Kronometroaren orria</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Sekuntikellosivu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Page de minuteur</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Páxina do cronómetro.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד שעון עצר</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">विराम घड़ी पृष्ठ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Stopper oldal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Pagina de Campana de Horologio (stopwatch)</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Halaman stopwatch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Pagina del cronometro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">სხვანაირი წამმზომის გვერდი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">초시계 쪽</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Chronometro puslapis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Hronometra lapa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Pagina met stopwatch</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Stoppeklokke-side</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਸਟਾਪਵਾਚ ਸਫ਼ਾ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Strona stopera</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Página de Cronómetro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Página do cronômetro</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Pagina cronometrului</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Страница секундомера</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">स्टॉपवॉच पृष्ठ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Stran štoparice</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Sida med stoppur</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kronometre sayfası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Сторінка секундоміра</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">秒表页面</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">碼錶頁面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kclock/kclock-mobile-stopwatch.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Alarms page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">ساعة المنبه</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="bg">Страница с аларми</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Pàgina de les alarmes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Pàgina de les alarmes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Stránka s upomínkami</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="da">Alarmersiden</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Weckerseite</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Σελίδα συναγερμών</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Alarms page</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Paĝo de alarmoj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Página de alarmas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Alarmen orria</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Hälytyssivu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Page d'alarmes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Páxina das alarmas.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">עמוד התראות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">अलार्मों का पृष्ठ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Riasztás oldal</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Pagina de alarma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Halaman alarm</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Pagina degli allarmi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მაღვიძარის გვერდი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">알람 쪽</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lt">Žadintuvų puslapis</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="lv">Signālu lapa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Pagina met alarmen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nn">Alarmside</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pa">ਅਲਾਰਮ ਸਫ਼ਾ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Strona alarmów</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Página de Alarmes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Página do alarme</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ro">Pagina alarmelor</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Страница напоминаний</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">अलार्म पृष्ठ</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Stran alarma</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Sida med alarm</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Alarmlar sayfası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Сторінка будильників</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">闹钟页面</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">鬧鐘頁面</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kclock/kclock-mobile-alarms.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Utility</category>
    <category>Clock</category>
    <category>KDE</category>
  </categories>
  <provides>
    <binary>kclock</binary>
    <binary>kclockd</binary>
    <dbus type="user">org.kde.kclockd</dbus>
  </provides>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/kclock/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/describecomponents.cgi?product=KClock</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kclock&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/utilities/kclock</url>
  <releases>
    <release version="25.12.2" date="2026-02-05"/>
    <release version="25.12.1" date="2026-01-08"/>
    <release version="25.12.0" date="2025-12-11"/>
    <release version="25.08.3" date="2025-11-06"/>
    <release version="25.08.2" date="2025-10-09"/>
    <release version="25.08.1" date="2025-09-11"/>
    <release version="25.08.0" date="2025-08-14"/>
    <release version="25.04.3" date="2025-07-03"/>
    <release version="25.04.2" date="2025-06-05"/>
    <release version="25.04.1" date="2025-05-08"/>
    <release version="25.04.0" date="2025-04-17"/>
    <release version="24.12.3" date="2025-03-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.2" date="2025-02-06"/>
    <release version="24.12.1" date="2025-01-09"/>
    <release version="24.12.0" date="2024-12-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07"/>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10"/>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12"/>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22"/>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04"/>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13"/>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23"/>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11"/>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21"/>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28"/>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
    <release version="23.08.4" date="2023-12-07"/>
    <release version="23.08.3" date="2023-11-09"/>
    <release version="23.08.2" date="2023-10-12"/>
    <release version="23.08.1" date="2023-09-14"/>
    <release version="23.08.0" date="2023-08-24"/>
    <release version="23.04.3" date="2023-07-06"/>
    <release version="23.04.2" date="2023-06-08"/>
    <release version="23.04.1" date="2023-05-11"/>
    <release version="23.04.0" date="2023-04-20"/>
    <release version="23.01" date="2023-01-30">
      <url>https://plasma-mobile.org/2023/01/30/january-blog-post/</url>
      <description>
        <p>New features and bugfixes in this release:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">ميزات جديدة وإصلاحات علل في هذا الإصدار:</p>
        <p xml:lang="bg">Нови възможности и корекция на грешки в това издание:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques noves i correccions d'errors en aquesta versió:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques noves i esmenes d'errors en esta versió:</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Nuevas funciones y corrección de fallos de esta versión:</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">יכולות ותיקוני תקלות חדשים במהדורה הזאת:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ia">Nove characteristicas e correctiones de faltas in iste version:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ახალი ფუნქციები და შეცდომების გასწორება ამ ვერსიაში:</p>
        <p xml:lang="nl">Nieuwe functies en reparaties van bugs in deze uitgave:</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Novas funcionalidades e correções de bugs nesta versão:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Новые возможности и исправления ошибок в этом выпуске:</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Nove zmožnosti in popravki napak v tej izdaji:</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">New features and bugfixes in this release:</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Нові можливості і виправлення вад у цьому випуску:</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-CN">此版本中的新功能和程序缺陷修复：</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed timer add one minute button.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاح زر إضافة دقيقة واحدة في المؤقت.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Corregeix el botó d'afegir un minut al temporitzador.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Corregix el botó d'afegir un minut al temporitzador.</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תוקן כפתור הוספת דקה לקוצב הזמן.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Corrigite que le chronometro adde button de un minuta.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა ტაიმერისთვის ერთი წუთის დამატების ღილაკი.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido botão para adicionar um minuto ao temporizador</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Кнопка добавления одной минуты к таймеру;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Popravljen časovnik gumb za dodaj eno minuto.</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Fixed timer add one minute button.</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Виправлено кнопку додавання однієї хвилини у таймері.</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">修复计时器增加一分钟按钮。</li>
          <li>Switched to tab bar based sidebar (similar to bottom navigation bar).</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">الانتقال إلى شريط جانبي يعتمد على شريط الألسنة (يشبه شريط التنقل السفلي).</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">S'ha canviat a una barra lateral basada en la barra de pestanyes (similar a la barra de navegació inferior).</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">S'ha canviat a una barra lateral basada en la barra de pestanyes (similar a la barra de navegació inferior).</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">סרגל הצד מבוסס לשוניות מעתה (בדומה לסרגל ניווט תחתון).</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Comjmutate a barra lateral basate sur barra de scheda (simile al barra de navigation a basso) </li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გადართვა ჩანართებზე ბაზირებულ გვერდით პანელზე (ქვედა ნავიგაციის პანელის მსგავსად).</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Alteração para uma barra lateral baseada em abas (semelhante à barra de navegação inferior).</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Переход на боковую панель с вкладками (аналогично нижней панели навигации);</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Preklopljeno na stransko vrstico, ki temelji na vrstici z zavihki (podobno kot spodnja navigacijska vrstica).</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Switched to tab bar based sidebar (similar to bottom navigation bar).</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Перехід на бічну панель із вкладками (подібну до панелі навігації унизу вікна).</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">切换到基于标签页栏的侧边栏 (类似于底部导航栏)。</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.11" date="2022-11-30">
      <url>https://plasma-mobile.org/2022/11/30/plasma-mobile-gear-22-11/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="22.09" date="2022-09-27">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/09/27/plasma-mobile-gear-22-09/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="22.06" date="2022-06-24">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/06/28/plasma-mobile-gear-22-06/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04" date="2022-04-26">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/04/26/plasma-mobile-gear-22-04/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Support for background daemon when using flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">دعم العفريت الخلفي عند استخدام flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Permet el dimoni en segon pla quan s'utilitza flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet el dimoni en segon pla quan s'utilitza flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תמיכה בפעולה כסוכן רקע בעת שימוש דרך flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Supporto per demone de fundo quando usante flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ფონური დემონის მხარდაჭერა flatpak-ის გამოყენებისას</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para daemon em segundo plano ao usar o Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка фоновой службы при использовании flatpak;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Podpora za demon ozadja pri uporabi flatpaka</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Support for background daemon when using flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Реалізовано підтримку фонової служби при використанні flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">使用 flatpak 时支持后台守护进程</li>
          <li>Fix excessive log generation on non-Plasma system</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاح توليد السجلات المفرط على الأنظمة غير المعتمدة على بلازما</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Corregeix la generació excessiva de registres en un sistema no Plasma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Corregix la generació excessiva de registres en un sistema no Plasma</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תוקנה יצירת רשומות יומן מוגזמות במערכות שאינן פלזמה</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Corrige generation excessive de log (registros) sur systema que non es de Plasma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა ზედმეტი ჟურნალის ჩანაწერების გენერაცია არა-Plasma სისტემებზე</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção de geração excessiva de logs em sistemas que não sejam Plasma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено избыточное создание журналов в системах без Plasma;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Popravljeno prekomerno ustvarjanje dnevnikov v sistemu, ki ni Plasma</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Fix excessive log generation on non-Plasma system</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Виправлено додавання зайвих повідомлень журналу у системах поза Плазмою</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">修复在非 Plasma 系统下过多的日志生成</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.02" date="2022-02-09">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2022/02/09/plasma-mobile-gear-22-02/</url>
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix "Clock daemon not found" popup message</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاح الرسالة المنبثقة "عفريت الساعة غير موجود"</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Corregeix el missatge emergent «No s'ha trobat el dimoni del rellotge»</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Corregix el missatge emergent «No s'ha trobat el dimoni del rellotge»</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תוקנה ההודעה הקופצת „סוכן השעון לא נמצא”</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Corrige message de popup "Demone de Clock (Horologio) non trovate" </li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა მხტუნარა შეტყობინება 'საათის დემონი აღმოჩენილი არაა'</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da mensagem pop-up "Daemon do relógio não encontrado"</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено сообщение «Не найден демон часов»;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Popravljeno pojavno sporočilo "Demon ure ni bil najden"</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Fix "Clock daemon not found" popup message</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Виправлено контекстне повідомлення «Не знайдено фонову службу годинника»</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">修复“时钟守护进程未找到”弹出消息</li>
          <li>Various bugfixes and user interface improvements</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاحات علل متنوعة وتحسينات في واجهة المستخدم</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Diverses correccions d'errors i millores de la interfície d'usuari</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Diverses esmenes d'errors i millores de la interfície d'usuari</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">מגוון תיקוני תקלות ושיפורים בממשק המשתמש</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Varie correctiones de faltas e melioramentos de interfacie de usator</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">მომხმარებლის ინტერფეისის გაუმჯობესება და შეცდომების გამოსწორება</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Diversas correções de bugs e melhorias na interface do usuário</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены ошибки и улучшен интерфейс;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Različni popravki napak in izboljšave uporabniškega vmesnika</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Various bugfixes and user interface improvements</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Різноманітні виправлення вад і удосконалення інтерфейсу користувача</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">各种程序缺陷修复和用户界面改进</li>
          <li>Add a sound picker component for listing alarm sounds</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إضافة مكون منتقي الصوت لسرد أصوات المنبه</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Afegeix un component de selector de so per a llistar els sons d'alarma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Afig un component de selector de so per a llistar els sons d'alarma</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">נוסף רכיב בורר שמע להצעת צלילי התזכורות</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Adde un componente selector de sono per listar sonos de alarma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">დაემატა ხმის არჩევის კომპონენტი განგაშის ხმების ჩამოსათვლელად</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionado um componente de seleção de som para listar sons de alarme</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлен компонент выбора звука для перечисления звуков будильника;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Dodana komponenta za izbiranje zvokov za seznam zvokov alarmov</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Add a sound picker component for listing alarm sounds</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Додано компонент вибору звукових даних для показу списку звуків будильника</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">新增声音选择器组件以列出可用的闹钟声音</li>
          <li>Start snooze only after button is pressed</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">بدء الغفو فقط بعد ضغط الزر</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Inicia el posposament només després de prémer el botó</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Inicia el posposament només després de prémer el botó</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">להתחיל נודניק אחר לאחר לחיצת הכפתור</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Initia snooze (dormettar) solmente post que le button es pressate</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გადადების დაწყება, მხოლოდ, ღილაკზე დაჭერის შემდეგ</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">A função soneca só inicia após o botão ser pressionado</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Запуск отложенного сигнала только после нажатия кнопки;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Zaženi dremež šele po pritisku gumba</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Start snooze only after button is pressed</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Реалізовано початок відліку відкладення будильника лише після натискання кнопки</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">仅在按下按钮后才开始贪睡</li>
          <li>Fix alarms not working on PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاح عدم عمل المنبهات على PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Corregeix les alarmes que no funcionen amb el PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Corregix les alarmes que no funcionen amb PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תוקנו התראות שלא עובדות ב־PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Corrige alarmas non functionante sur PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა განგაშების პრობლემა PinePhone-ზე</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção de alarmes que não funcionam no PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена неработающая сигнализация на PinePhone;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Popravi alarme, ki ne delujejo na PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Fix alarms not working on PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Виправлено непрацездатність будильника на PinePhone</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">修复闹钟无法在 PinePhone 上工作</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12" date="2021-12-07">
      <description>
        <p>Changes:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">تغييرات:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Canvis:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Canvis:</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Cambios:</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">שינויים:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ia">Modificationes:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ცვლილებები:</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Alterações:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Изменения:</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Spremembe:</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">Changes:</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Зміни:</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-CN">更改：</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Kirigami's bottom navigation bar component is now used for mobile</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">استخدام مكون شريط التنقل السفلي الخاص بـ Kirigami للمحمول</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">El component de la barra de navegació inferior del Kirigami ara s'utilitza per al mòbil</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">El component de la barra de navegació inferior de Kirigami ara s'utilitza per al mòbil</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Lecomponente de barra de navigation de basso de Kirigami es nunc usate per mobile</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ახლა მობილურისთვის გამოიყენება Kirigami-ის ქვედა ნავიგაციის კომპონენტი</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">O componente de barra de navegação inferior do Kirigami agora é usado na versão mobile</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Для мобильных устройств теперь используется компонент нижней панели навигации Kirigami;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Kirigamijeva komponenta spodnje navigacijske vrstice se zdaj uporablja za mobilne naprave</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Kirigami's bottom navigation bar component is now used for mobile</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Для мобільних систем у новій версії використано компонент нижньої панелі навігації з Kirigami</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">手机版使用 Kirigami 的底部导航栏组件</li>
          <li>A Plasma style sidebar is now used on desktop</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">استخدام شريط جانبي بنمط بلازما على سطح المكتب</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Ara s'utilitza una barra lateral d'estil Plasma a l'escriptori</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Ara s'utilitza una barra lateral d'estil Plasma a l'escriptori</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Un barra lateral de stilo dePlasmaes nunc usate sur scriptorio</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">სამუშაო მაგიდაზე ახლა Plasma-ის სტილის გვერდითი პანელი გამოიყენება</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Agora, no desktop, é utilizada uma barra lateral no estilo Plasma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">На рабочем столе теперь используется боковая панель в стиле Plasma;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Stranska vrstica v slogu Plasme se zdaj uporablja na namizju</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">A Plasma style sidebar is now used on desktop</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">У версії для робочих станцій тепер використано бічну панель у стилі Плазми</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">桌面版使用 Plasma 样式的侧边栏</li>
          <li>The system tray item now only shows when alarms are pending</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إظهار عنصر صينية النظام فقط عند وجود منبهات قيد الانتظار</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">L'element de la safata del sistema ara es mostra només quan les alarmes estan pendents</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'element de la safata del sistema ara es mostra només quan les alarmes estan pendents</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Le elemento de tabuliero de systema non solmente monstra quando alarmas es pendente</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ხატულს სისტემურ საათთან ახლა, მხოლოდ, ნაჩვენებია, თუ განგაშები რიგშია</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">O item da bandeja do sistema agora só é exibido quando há alarmes pendentes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Элемент в области уведомлений отображается только при наличии активных будильников;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Element v sistemski vrstici se zdaj prikaže le, ko so alarmi v teku</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">The system tray item now only shows when alarms are pending</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">У новій версії програма показує пункт системного лотка, лише якщо у черзі є будильники</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">系统托盘图标现在仅在有待发闹钟时显示</li>
          <li>The daemon automatically stops if no alarms and timers are pending</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إيقاف العفريت آلياً في حال عدم وجود منبهات أو مؤقتات معلقة</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">El dimoni s'atura automàticament si no hi ha alarmes ni temporitzadors pendents</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">El dimoni es para automàticament si no hi ha alarmes ni temporitzadors pendents</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Le demoine stoppa automaticamente si necun alarmas e chronometros (timers) es pendente</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">დემონი ავტომატურად გაჩერდება, თუ განგაშები და ტაიმერები რიგში არაა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">O serviço para automaticamente se não houver alarmes ou temporizadores pendentes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Служба автоматически останавливается, если нет активных будильников и таймеров;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Demon se samodejno ustavi, če ni alarmov in časovnikov v teku</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">The daemon automatically stops if no alarms and timers are pending</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Реалізовано автоматичне зупинення фонової служби, якщо у черзі немає будильників і таймерів</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">如果没有待发的闹钟和计时器，守护进程会自动停止</li>
          <li>Action bars are now used on the timer and alarms forms page</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">استخدام أشرطة الإجراءات في صفحة نماذج المؤقت والمنبهات</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Les barres d'acció ara s'utilitzen a la pàgina del formulari del temporitzador i les alarmes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Les barres d'acció ara s'utilitzen a la pàgina del formulari del temporitzador i les alarmes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Barras de action es nunc usate sur le pagina de formas de chronometro e alarmas </li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">ქმედებების პანელები ახლა გამოიყენება ტაიმერისა და განგაშის ფორმების გვერდზე</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Agora, as barras de ação são usadas nas páginas de formulários de temporizador e alarmes</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">На страницах таймера и будильников теперь используются панели действий;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Vrstice dejanj se zdaj uporabljajo na strani obrazcev za časovnik in alarme</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Action bars are now used on the timer and alarms forms page</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">У новій версії на сторінці таймерів та будильників використано панелі кнопок дій</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">操作栏现在被用于计时器和闹钟表单页面</li>
          <li>The settings button has been moved to the top actions bar</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">نقل زر الإعدادات إلى شريط الإجراءات العلوي</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">El botó de configuració s'ha mogut a la barra d'accions superior</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">El botó de configuració s'ha mogut cap a la barra d'accions superior</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Le button de preferentias ha essite movite al barra de actiones de culmine</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">მორგების ღილაკი გადატანილია ზედა ქმედებების პანელზე</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">O botão de configurações foi movido para a barra de ações superior</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Кнопка настроек перемещена в верхнюю панель действий;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Gumb za nastavitve je bil premaknjen v zgornjo vrstico z dejanji</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">The settings button has been moved to the top actions bar</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Кнопку параметрів пересунуто на верхню панель кнопок дій</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">设置按钮已被移动到顶部操作栏</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/12/07/plasma-mobile-gear-21-12/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08" date="2021-08-31">
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/08/31/plasma-mobile-gear-21-08/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.07" date="2021-07-20">
      <description>
        <p>Changes:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">تغييرات:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Canvis:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Canvis:</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Cambios:</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">שינויים:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ia">Modificationes:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ცვლილებები:</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Alterações:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Изменения:</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Spremembe:</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">Changes:</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Зміни:</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-CN">更改：</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Watch DBus for PowerDevil, so wake from suspend always works if PowerDevil is found</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">مراقبة DBus لـ PowerDevil، ليعمل الاستيقاظ من التعليق دائماً في حال وُجد PowerDevil</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Vigila el DBus del PowerDevil, de manera que despertar de la suspensió sempre funciona si es troba el PowerDevil</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vigila D-Bus de PowerDevil, de manera que despertar de la suspensió sempre funciona si es troba PowerDevil</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Observa DBus per PowerDevil, assi que evelia ex suspende functiona sempre si PowerDevil es trovate</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">PowerDevil-ის ლოდინი DBus-ზე, ასე რომ, გაღვიძება ყოველთვის მუშაობს, თუ PowerDevil აღმოჩენილია</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Monitora o DBus em busca de PowerDevil, para que a ativação a partir da suspensão sempre funcione se PowerDevil for encontrado</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Отслеживание DBus для PowerDevil, чтобы пробуждение из режима приостановки всегда работало при наличии PowerDevil;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Pazite na DBus za PowerDevil, zato prebujanje iz stanja pripravljenosti vedno deluje, če je PowerDevil najden</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Watch DBus for PowerDevil, so wake from suspend always works if PowerDevil is found</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Реалізовано спостереження DBus для PowerDevil, отже пробудження від присипляння завжди працюватиме, якщо буде виявлено PowerDevil</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">监视 DBus 中的 PowerDevil，如果发现 PowerDevil，则从挂起状态中唤醒</li>
          <li>Use consistent dialog style on the settings page</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">استخدام نمط حوار متسق في صفحة الإعدادات</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Usa un estil de diàleg coherent a la pàgina de configuració</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Utilitza un estil de diàleg coherent a la pàgina de configuració</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Usa dialogo de stilo consistente sur le pagina de preferentias</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">მუდმივი დიალოგის სტილის გამოყენება მორგების გვერდზე</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Uso de um estilo de diálogo consistente na página de configurações</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Используется единый стиль диалогов на странице настроек;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Uporabi dosleden slog dialoga na strani z nastavitvami</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Use consistent dialog style on the settings page</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Реалізовано однорідний стиль вікон на сторінці параметрів</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在设置页面使用一致的对话框样式</li>
          <li>After editing an alarm, the alarm now automatically is activated</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">تنشيط المنبه آلياً بعد تحريره</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Després d'editar una alarma, l'alarma ara s'activa automàticament</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Després d'editar una alarma, l'alarma ara s'activa automàticament</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Post modficar un alarma, le alarma es nunc activate automaticamente</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">განგაშის ჩასწორების შემდეგ, ახლა, განგაში ავტომატურად გააქტიურდება</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Após editar um alarme, ele agora é ativado automaticamente</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">После редактирования будильник автоматически активируется;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Po urejanju alarma je alarm zdaj samodejno aktiviran</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">After editing an alarm, the alarm now automatically is activated</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Реалізовано автоматичну активацію будильника після його редагування</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在编辑闹钟后自动激活它</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/07/20/plasma-mobile-gear-21-07/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.06" date="2021-06-10">
      <description>
        <p>New features and bugfixes:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ar">ميزات جديدة وإصلاحات علل:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques noves i correccions d'errors:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques noves i esmenes d'errors:</p>
        <p xml:lang="es">Nuevas funciones y corrección de fallos:</p>
        <p xml:lang="he">יכולות חדשות ותיקוני תקלות:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ia">Nove characteristicas e correctiones de faltas:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ka">ახალი ფუნქციები და შეცდომების გასწორებები:</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Novas funcionalidades e correções de bugs:</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Новые возможности и исправления ошибок:</p>
        <p xml:lang="sl">Nove zmožnosti in popravki napak:</p>
        <p xml:lang="tr">New features and bugfixes:</p>
        <p xml:lang="uk">Нові можливості і виправлення вад:</p>
        <p xml:lang="zh-CN">新功能和程序缺陷修复：</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Added the ability to set timer presets</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إضافة القدرة على ضبط مسبقات المؤقت</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">S'ha afegit la capacitat d'establir valors predefinits del temporitzador</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">S'ha afegit la capacitat d'establir valors predefinits del temporitzador</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">נוספה האפשרות להגדיר תצורות קוצב זמן</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Addite lehabilitate de assignar preinsimules de chronometro (timer presets)</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">დაემატა ტაიმერის პრესეტების დაყენების შესაძლებლობა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionada a capacidade de definir predefinições de temporizador</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена возможность настройки предустановок таймера;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Dodana je možnost nastavitve prednastavitev časovnika</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Added the ability to set timer presets</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Додано можливість встановлення наборів таймерів</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">新增设置计时器预设的功能</li>
          <li>Added ability to increase timer duration by 1m as timer is running</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إضافة القدرة على زيادة مدة المؤقت بمقدار دقيقة واحدة أثناء تشغيله</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">S'ha afegit la capacitat d'augmentar la durada del temporitzador en 1 m quan s'està executant el temporitzador</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">S'ha afegit la capacitat d'augmentar la duració del temporitzador en 1 m quan s'està executant el temporitzador</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">נוספה אפשרות להגדיר את משך קוצב הזמן בדקה בזמן שקוצב הזמן רץ</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Addite habilitate a augmentar duration de chronometro per 1m durante que le chronometro es executante</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">დაემატა ტაიმერის ხანგრძლივობის ერთი წუთით გაზრდის საშუალება, როცა ტაიმერი გაშვებულია</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionada a capacidade de aumentar a duração do temporizador em 1 minuto enquanto ele estiver em execução</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена возможность увеличивать длительность таймера на 1 минуту во время его работы;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Dodana možnost podaljšanja trajanja časovnika za 1 minuto med delovanjem časovnika</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Added ability to increase timer duration by 1m as timer is running</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Додано можливість збільшувати тривалість відліку на 1 хвилину під час роботи таймера</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">新增了在计时器运行时将其时长增加 1 分钟的功能</li>
          <li>Fixed multiple alarm sounds and notifications being played for one alarm</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاح تشغيل أصوات منبه وإشعارات متعددة لمنبه واحد</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Corregits diversos sons d'alarma i notificacions que es reprodueixen per a una alarma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Corregits diversos sons d'alarma i notificacions que es reproduïxen per a una alarma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Corrigite que multiple notificationes e sonos de alarma es executate perun alarma</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა ერთზე მეტი განგაშისა და შეტყობინების ხმის ერთდროული დაკვრა ერთი განგაშისთვის</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema de reprodução simultânea de múltiplos sons de alarme e notificações para um mesmo alarme</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено воспроизведение нескольких звуков и уведомлений для одного будильника;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Popravljeno predvajanje več zvokov alarmov in obvestil za en alarm</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Fixed multiple alarm sounds and notifications being played for one alarm</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Виправлено проблему, пов'язану із тим, що для одного будильника відтворювалося декілька звуків будильника і нагадувань</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">修复了一个闹钟触发时多次响起提示音和通知的问题</li>
          <li>Fixed errors that prevented the application from working in a Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ar">إصلاح الأخطاء التي منعت التطبيق من العمل في Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca">Corregits els errors que impedien que l'aplicació funcionés en un Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Corregits els errors que impedien que l'aplicació funcionara en un Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="he">תוקנו שגיאות שמנעו מהיישום לעבוד ב־Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ia">Corrigite errores que preveniva le application ab functionar in un Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ka">გასწორდა შეცდომები, რომლებიც აპლიკაციას Flatpak-ში მუშაობის საშუალებას არ აძლევდა</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigidos erros que impediam o funcionamento do aplicativo em um Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены ошибки, препятствовавшие работе приложения в Flatpak;</li>
          <li xml:lang="sl">Popravljene napake, ki so preprečevale delovanje aplikacije v Flatpaku</li>
          <li xml:lang="tr">Fixed errors that prevented the application from working in a Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Виправлено помилки, які заважали роботі програми у Flatpak</li>
          <li xml:lang="zh-CN">修复了妨碍应用程序在 Flatpak 中工作的错误</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
      <url>https://www.plasma-mobile.org/2021/06/10/plasma-mobile-update-june/</url>
    </release>
    <release version="21.05" date="2021-05-10"/>
  </releases>
</component>
